现在情况怎样?
How we doing, Richard?
我们会提早十五分钟 越过英国海岸
We should pass over the English coast 15 minutes ahead of time, sir.
以我们背载的货品来说 成绩很不俗
Well, with this load on our back, that's good going.
皇家空军 值得信赖
Just trust the RAF, sir.
- 搞什么鬼?  - 太空梭点火了
- What the hell is that? - The shuttle ignition.
- 消失了?  - 垦月者号怎么了?
- Disappeared? - And what happened to the Moonraker?
天啊
Good God.
当然了 首相 我马上办
Yes, yes, of course, Minister. Right away.
钱班霓 007从非洲回来了没?
Moneypenny, is 007 back from that African job?
他还有一项任务在身
He's on his last leg, sir.
再高一点 我的耳朵就会爆裂
Any higher, Mr. Bond, my ears will pop.
我想我不会再跟别人 一起搭飞机了
I don't think I'm ever going to fly with anyone else.
你说得对极了 邦德先生
You're so right, Mr. Bond.
我们就把你就留在这里 邦德先生
This is where we leave you, Mr. Bond.
太仓促了吧?
A little premature, isn't it?
祝你旅途愉快
Enjoy your flight.
《007系列之太空城》
- 早安 钱班霓 - 詹姆斯
- Good morning, Moneypenny. - James.
你怎么这么晚?
But why are you so late?
我没穿降落伞从飞机上掉下来
I fell out of an airplane without a parachute.
- 谁在里面?  - Q和国防部长
- Who's in there? - Q and the Minister of Defense.
你不相信我吧?
You don't believe me, do you?
- 快进去吧 - 是的 钱班霓
- And you should go right in. - Yes, Moneypenny.
- 终于来了 007 - 早安
- 007. At last. - Good morning, sir.
他是国防部长佛雷克葛瑞
I think you know Frederick Gray, Minister of Defense.
- 中校 - 部长 Q
- Commander. - Minister. Q.
007啊
007.
垦月者号?
Moonraker?
- 你对垦月者号知道多少?  - 我只在报章上看过 长官
- What do you know about Moonraker? - What I read in the newspaper, sir.
那么你知道 
Then you'll know that Moonraker, the space shuttle,
我们正在用747客机
was being flown over here
运送美国人借我们的 垦月者号到这儿来
on loan from the Americans on the back of a 747.
飞机在育康坠毁
Yes, which crashed somewhere in the Yukon,
飞机和太空梭完全毁掉 对吗?
aircraft and shuttle totally destroyed, correct?
- 这是官方的版本 - 实情令人困扰
- That's the official version. - The truth is rather more disturbing, 007.
你看
Look at this.
这里是坠机现场 残骸撒落的范围广阔
Now, that's the scene of the crash. Wreckage strewn over a large area.
机身就只剩下这么多
That's all that's left of the fuselage.
我们已彻底搜查过
We've been through it with a fine-toothed comb,
却没发现垦月者号的残骸
but there's no sign of Moonraker, not a trace.
你是说太空梭在半空被劫持?
Are you suggesting the shuttle was hijacked in midair?
这就交给你去调查了
That's for you to find out, 007.
太空梭是由 在加州的崔斯工业制造
The shuttles are built in California by Drax Industries.
对 我们负责 这太空梭的安全 指挥官
Yes. We were responsible for the safety of that shuttle, Commander.
美国政府相当关注这件事
The United States government is justifiably concerned.
我想像得到 从加州开始调查
I can imagine. Then, California must be the place to start.
- 同意 - 千万别出错 007
- I agree. - Don't make any mistakes, 007.
这次的情况相当严重 我们必须把太空梭找回来
The situation is critical. We've got to find that shuttle.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
若没有其他问题
If that's all, gentlemen...
等一下 我有东西给你
Just a minute, 007. I've got something for you.
把右边的袖子卷起来 好吗?
Roll up your right sleeve, will you?
现在这快成为标准装备了
This is now being issued as standard equipment.
把它系在腕上
Strap it on your wrist.
它是由腕肌肉神经冲脉启动的
It's activated by nerve impulses from the wrist muscles.
像这样?
Like this?
谢谢 007!
Oh, thank you, 007.
- 你小心点 好吗?  - 知道
- Be careful, will you? - Yes, Q.
共有十枚镖 五枚蓝色的 可以穿透盔甲
Ten darts, five blue-tipped with armor piercing heads,
五枚红色的渗有氰化物 半分钟内致人于死
five red-tipped, cyanide coated, causing death in 30 seconds.
非常新奇 在圣诞礼品店购买的吗?
Very novel, Q. You must get them in the stores for Christmas.
各位再见
Good morning, gentlemen.
- 欢迎来到加州 邦德先生 - 我已经爱上这里了
- Welcome to California, Mr. Bond. - I like it already.
我叫柯琳杜弗尔
My name is Corinne Dufour.
你会带我四处参观吗?
Oh, and you're going to be showing me around, are you, Corinne?
不 我只是崔斯企业的 一个谦卑驾驶员
No. I'm just a humble pilot in the service of the Drax Corporation.
这是崔斯庄园 你看到的一切都属于崔斯先生
This is the Drax estate now. Everything you see belongs to Mr. Drax.
- 他拥有很多 不是吗?  - 他想要的都已经有了
- Owns a lot, doesn't he? - What he doesn't own, he doesn't want.
我们快到主建筑物了
We're approaching the main complex now.
垦月者号 就是在这里制造的吗?
That's where the Moonraker shuttle is made?
对 工场 飞机库
That's right, workshops, hangars,
设计和实验大楼 检验中心等等
design and experimental blocks, test centers, everything.
令人印象深刻
Very impressive.
听说雨果崔斯 很沉迷于征服宇宙
I'd heard that Hugo Drax is obsessed with the conquest of space.
我现在相信了 老天
Now, I can believe it. Good Lord.
崔斯大宅 一砖一瓦均购自法国
The Drax residence. Every stone brought from France.
- 很可爱 不是吗?  - 很宏伟
- Cute, isn't it? - Magnificent.
他何不连艾菲尔铁塔也买下?
Why didn't he buy the Eiffel Tower as well?
他有 只是法国政府不让铁塔出口
He did, but the French government refused him an export permit.
你看 她们是正在受训的太空人
Look there. Those are the astronaut trainees.
崔斯先生独力资助 这个训练计划
Mr. Drax is financing the entire training program out of his own pocket.
他的投资眼光非常独到
He seems to have an eye for a good investment.
崔斯先生会在划厅 接见邦德先生 杜弗尔小姐
Mr. Drax will see Mr. Bond in the drawing room, Miss Dufour.
- 谢谢你 - 这边走
- Thank you, Cavendish. - This way, please, sir.
邦德先生来了
Mr. Bond, sir.
- 邦德先生 - 崔斯先生
- Mr. Bond. - Mr. Drax.
在她们离开前 容我介绍 鲁宝斯基女伯爵
Allow me to present, before they leave us, Countess Lubinski,
你们好吗?
How do you do?
我们久仰大名
Well, my dear fellow, your reputation precedes you, of course.
很荣幸贵国政府派你负责 这个微妙的任务
I'm honored that your government should send you on so delicate a mission.
微妙 崔斯先生?
Delicate, Mr. Drax?
亲身前来为我的损失道歉
Well, to apologize in person for the loss of my space shuttle.
王尔德会怎么说?
How would Oscar Wilde have put it?
"损失一艘飞机也许是不幸"
"To lose one aircraft may be regarded as a misfortune,
"损失两艘就是粗心大意"
"to lose two seems like carelessness."
崔斯先生 当我们调查出 垦月者号的下落后
Well, an apology will be made to the American government, Mr. Drax,
我国自会向美国政府道歉
when we've discovered why there was no trace of the Moonraker in that wreckage.
你的忠诚真值得尊敬 邦德先生
And your loyalty commands respect, Mr. Bond.
你在一个非常适合的时候来到
You have arrived at a propitious moment,
这是贵国对西方文化的
coincident with your country's one indisputable contribution
重大贡献
to Western civilization.
下午茶
Afternoon tea.
- 你要吃黄瓜三明治吗?  - 谢谢 我不吃了
- May I press you to a cucumber sandwich? - Thank you, no, nothing at all.
整艘太空梭 是在加州制造的吗?
The shuttle, is it made entirely here in California?
不 我在世界各地的子公司
No. I own a number of subsidiaries throughout the world,
生产零件
producing components.
要征服宇宙 必须为人类的将来
The conquest of space represents an investment in the future
作出投资 邦德先生
of the entire human race, Mr. Bond.
所以要尽取各国之长处
It is, therefore, logical to seek out the best that each nation has to offer.
- 你是说人还是技术?  - 两者都是
- Are you referring to people or skills? - Both, Mr. Bond.
- 我来得太早了吗?  - 一点都不会
- Am I too soon? - Not at all.
我确定邦德先生 很渴望开始参观
I'm sure Mr. Bond is eager to start his tour.
杜佛尔小姐 会带你见向导妙算博士
Miss Dufour will escort you to Dr. Goodhead who will show you around.
有什么问题尽管发问
Ask anything you like.
- 谢谢你的合作 - 别客气
- Thank you for being so cooperative. - A pleasure.
你去照顾邦德先生 要确定他会有危险
Look after Mr. Bond. See that some harm comes to him.
妙算博士就在右边第一间房间
You'll find Dr. Goodhead first on the right.
- 谢谢你的指引 - 有什么需要 请随便吩咐
- Oh. Thank you for the ride. - Call on me if you need anything.
午安
Good afternoon.
- 有何贵干?  - 是的 我叫邦德
- Can I help you? - Yes. My name is Bond.
詹姆斯邦德 我找妙算博士
James Bond. I'm looking for Dr. Goodhead.
- 你刚刚找到她 - 是个女人
- You just found her. - A woman.
你的观察力果然名不虚传 邦德先生
Your powers of observation do you credit, Mr. Bond.
我的朋友叫我做詹姆斯
James, to my friends.
荷莉妙算
Holly Goodhead.
- 你在这里接受太空人训练吗?  - 我已接受过全盘训练
- Are you training to be an astronaut? - I'm fully trained.
我是从太空总署 太空管理部被借来的
On loan from NASA, the Space Administration.
邦德先生 我想我们最好开始吧
Well, Mr. Bond, I guess we'd better get started.
你不想浪费时间 和失去垦月者号 不是吗?
You don't want to lose time as well as a space shuttle, do you?
这就是垦月者号
This is it, the Moonraker.
可以用火箭发射到太空 或者
Capable of being launched into space by rocket...
或者围绕地球运行 再重返太空
Orbiting the Earth and reentering the atmosphere to land
像普通飞机般降落
like any conventional aircraft.
这是训练用的离心机
This is the centrifuge training.
模拟在太空时的重力状态
It simulates the gravity force you feel when shot into space.
速度由上面的指导员控制
The speed is controlled by the instructor from up there.
你何不试试?
Why not try it?
有何不可?
Why not?
- 牢牢扣好 - 知道 博士
- Strap yourself in firmly. - Yes, Doctor.
现在 你的手臂
Now your arms.
这是预防你把自己打昏的
That's to prevent you from knocking yourself out.
原来如此
I see.
速度有多快?
How fast does it go?
最高可达二十度重力 但那足以致命
It can go up to 20 Gs, but that would be fatal.
三度重力相等于 飞机起飞的压力
Three Gs is equivalent to take-off pressure.
很多人会在七度时昏过去
Most people pass out at seven.
你会是个很好的推销员
You make a great saleswoman.
你不用担心 我们叫这个是"胆小鬼的按钮"
You don't have to worry. This is what we call a "Chicken Switch."
你把手指放在按钮上
You just keep your finger on that button,
当你感到压力过大时 一按下
the moment the pressure gets too much for you, release the button
- 就会把电流给截断 - 就这样简单?
- and the power's cut off. - Just like that?
连70岁的老人家 也可以抵受三度重力
Come on, Mr. Bond. A 70-year-old can take 3 Gs.
问题是 你要找个七十岁老翁不容易
Well, the trouble is there is never a 70-year-old around when you need one.
- 你找我吗?  - 崔斯先生请你给他电话
- You want me? - Mr. Drax says to telephone him.
我到办公室去打电话 你开始吧 我很快回来
All right, I'll call him from my office. You go ahead. I'll be right back.
指导员会监督整个过程 好好享受
The instructor will supervise the session. Enjoy yourself.
是的 我们正好好招待他
Yes. We're taking good care of him.
我真不知道会发生什么事
I don't know what could've happened.
一定是操纵装置出了问题
Something must've gone wrong with the controls.
我来帮你
Let me help you.
妈妈给了我一张列明 首次约会不能做的清单
My mother gave me a list of things not to do on a first date.
你用不着了 我并非为那个而来
Maybe you won't need it. That's not what I came for.
那你要什么?
No. What do you want then?
我要找资料 这会让你心碎吗?
Would your feelings be shattered if I were to say information?
- 为什么我要告诉你任何事情?  - 为什么?
- Why should I tell you anything? - Why, indeed?
你太放肆了 邦德先生
You presume a great deal, Mr. Bond.
除了制造垦月者号 和训练太空人外
What goes on here besides the manufacture of Moonraker?
这里还有什么事?
And the astronaut training program?
这里还有其他实验室 但现在没有什么大事
There are other laboratories, but not much is happening now.
没了?
No?
从前曾进行机密的实验 但一切都被移走了
They were working on something very secret, but everything's been moved.
移到哪去了?
Where to?
不知道
I don't know.
那你妈妈的清单怎么办?
What about that list of your mother's?
我从来都不认识字
I never learned to read.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
你把我寻找资料的 欲望刺激起来
You whetted my appetite for information.
这里有保险箱吗? 谢谢
Is there a safe in here? Thank you.
不要!
James, no.
好惊人!
That's amazing.
在这里 看到了吗?  你拥有一个黄金心灵
There you are, you see? You have a heart of gold.
十八开的
Eighteen karat.
你必须离开
You must go.
你先走 我去把灯关上
Well, you go first. I'll turn off the lights.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 好好保重 - 你也是
- Take care of yourself. - And you.
亲爱的邦德先生
Ah, my dear Bond.
她们是黛莉笛儿小姐 和麦托小姐
This is Mademoiselle Deladier and La Signorina del Mateo.
- 你们好 - 吃午饭时再见
- Ladies. - I'll see you at lunch.
真可惜你要离开 这是好运动
A pity you leave us. Such good sport.
除非你是雉鸡
Unless you're a pheasant.
真是的 邦德先生.用我的枪吧 会有迷途小鸟飞过
Really, Mr. Bond. Take my gun, a stray bird may fly over.
我来是要谢谢你的款待
I only stopped to thank you for your hospitality.
弗瑞瑟会来得及送你到机场去
Fraser will get you to the airport in plenty of time.
来吧
Come now.
- 我的技术可不及你 - 你太谦虚了 邦德先生
- I doubt if I'm in your class. - Oh, you're too modest, Mr. Bond.
在那边
Over there.
你射歪了 邦德先生
You missed, Mr. Bond.
是吗?
Did I?
如你所说 真是好运动
As you said, such good sport.
你找我吗?
You called for me, Mr. Drax.
昨晚你跟邦德在我的书房里
You were with Bond last night in my study.
不是的 我...
No, I...
- 你把保险箱的位置告诉他 - 我没有!
- You showed him the safe. - I didn't.
我解雇你 你马上离开
I'm terminating your employment. You will leave immediately.
我会告诉你在哪里接我
Franco, I'll call you to tell you where to meet me.
我能为你介绍些什么东西吗?
Could I interest you in something?
我本来马上就想说有
Why, I'm tempted to say yes immediately.
但我还是先到处看看
But I think maybe I'd better have a look around.
请随便参观
Please. Go anywhere you wish.
1965年 维里尼博物馆和玻璃厂
And in 1955, the Venini Museum and Glass Works
为崔斯工业所收购
was taken over by Drax Industries.
这些是最罕见的
And here, ladies and gentlemen, we have some of the rarest examples
玻璃艺术品
of the glassblower's art.
每件作品都是由人工制造
As you know, everything was done absolutely by hand.
这个花瓶是在 1850至1860年期间
Here is a vase done by Lorenzo Graziati,
由蓝兰索贾西亚帝制造的 请跟我到这边来
sometime between 1850 and 1860. If you'd like to follow me over here.
这个精致的碗约在450年前
This exquisite bowl was fashioned about 1520, over 450 years ago.
也就是1520年非常流行
If it ever came on the market, it would certainly fetch a price
它的市价超过一百万美元
in excess of one million American dollars.
不过若有人想顺手牵羊的话
But if any of you are thinking of taking it...
这个七世纪初的盘子
Now, we have here a very early 17th century dish
绘有海蓝大奖章
with an aquamarine medallion.
这边有一件很有趣的东西
Over here, we have something very, very interesting.
这柄是世上独一无二的剑
This glass-handled sword,
剑柄是以玻璃铸造的
the only one of its kind in the world,
在18世纪末 由曼诺帝将军拥有
was owned by General Menotti in the late 18th century
是本厂的创办人的杰作
and is the work of Bruno...
十四世纪作品
14th century.
妙算博士
Dr. Goodhead.
希望你的出现只是巧合 邦德先生
I can only hope your presence here is a coincidence, Mr. Bond.
- 我讨厌被人跟踪 - 有谁不是
- I dislike being spied on. - Well, don't we all?
你住在丹尼里饭店吧?
You're staying at the Danieli, aren't you?
- 是的 你怎么知道?  - 我喜欢获得最新消息
- Yes. How did you know? - Well, I like to keep abreast of things.
恕我冒昧 你来威尼斯干嘛?
May I ask what you're doing in Venice?
我要对欧州太空委员会 进行演讲
I'm addressing a seminar of the European Space Commission.
真深奥
My, heavy stuff.
我总是忘了
But there again, I keep forgetting that you are
你不只是个美女
more than just a very beautiful woman.
若你要讨好我 别浪费时间了
If you're trying to be ingratiating, Mr. Bond, don't bother.
我可有更重要的事要想
I have more important things on my mind.
我正要跟你谈这个
Ah, that's what I'd like to talk to you about.
- 一起吃晚饭吧?  - 晚上我要演说
- Dinner this evening? - This evening I'm giving my address.
演说完后喝一杯 你没理由拒绝我吧?
Well, then, can you think of reason why we don't have a drink afterwards?
现在没有 晚一点一定有
Not immediately. But I'm sure I shall.
法国人
Franco.
再弹一次吧
Play it again, Sam.
- 你在这里干嘛?  - 恢复元气
- What the hell are you doing here? - Convalescing.
你的朋友查治要杀我
Your friend Cha just tried to kill me.
我跟这有关系?
And you think I had something to do with it?
我突然闪过这念头罢了
Well, the thought had flashed across my mind.
- 崔斯在那实验室里干什么?  - 你何不亲自问他?
- What's Drax up to in that laboratory? - Why don't you ask him yourself?
- 你会把你的电话号码给我吗?  - 我不觉得这是必要的
- You leaving me your telephone number? - I don't see the point.
我明白了
Ah, now I do.
今晚不打算遇上这种事
Not what I want to get stuck with tonight.
你为什么不自己去倒杯酒喝?
James, why don't you pour yourself a drink?
谢谢
Thank you.
"日志"
Daily diary.
是死亡日志
Fairly deadly diary.
博林格尔? 如果是六九年的 那你就在等我
Bollinger. If it's '69, you were expecting me.
这玩意儿盖过了你的香味
Trifle overpowering, your scent.
标准的中央情报局装备
Standard CIA equipment.
他们派你混入崔斯吧?
And the CIA placed you with Drax, correct?
- 你很聪明 - 并不是
- Very astute of you, James. - Oh, not really.
我有些基层的朋友
I have friends in low places.
我们可以交换资料吗?
Could this possibly be the moment for us to pool our resources?
这样做会有补偿
It could have its compensations.
你打算到哪去?
Where are you planning on going from here?
我没打算离开
I'm not planning on going anywhere.
你说得对 我们合作 效果会更好
Oh, I suppose you're right, Holly. We would be better off working together.
- 缓和紧张关系?  - 同意
- Detente? - Agreed.
- 互相谅解?  - 也许吧
- Understanding? - Possibly.
- 共同合作?  - 可能吧
- Cooperation? - Maybe.
- 彼此信任?  - 不可能的
- Trust? - Out of the question.
马上叫服务员来替我拿行李
Send the night porter up for my bags immediately, please.
希望你知道自己在干嘛 我曾经跟他打桥牌的
I hope you know what you're doing, Bond. I've played bridge with this fellow Drax.
若非事关重大 007也不会惊动我们
007 doesn't usually push the panic button unless it's something serious.
- 但愿如此 - 早安
- I should hope not. - Good morning, Inspector.
- 早 - 你已经跟我们的意大利朋友
- Good morning. - I see you've covered everything
- 把这里掩饰好了 - 是的
- with our Italian friends. - Yes, sir.
- 是这个吗?  - 是的
- Is this it? - Yes, sir.
防毒面具?
Gas masks?
我们不可以冒险的
We can't afford to take any chances, Minister.
佛雷克葛瑞 真是意外!
Frederick Gray. What a surprise.
在著名的公司里 戴上防毒面具
And in distinguished company, all wearing gas masks.
很抱歉 由于我不是英国人
You must excuse me, gentlemen, not being English,
真的无法欣赏你们的幽默感
I sometimes find your sense of humor rather difficult to follow.
我代表英国政府 向你致歉
On behalf of the British government, I apologize.
你得解释清楚 007
I think you owe us an explanation, 007.
我这辈子从没受过如此的屈辱
I've never been so humiliated in my life.
我要解除他这次的职务
Your man should be taken off the assignment.
领事馆里见吧
I'll see you at the consulate.
我得听从他的指示
I'll have to do what he says.
在你执行任务之前 请叫Q把这个进行分析
Well, before you do that, sir, have Q do an analysis of this.
我从实验室里拿来的
I took it from the laboratory.
叫他千万要小心 这是极其危险的
Tell him to exercise extreme caution. It is lethal.
原来真的有实验室
So, there was a laboratory.
你先休息两个星期吧 007
You better take two weeks leave of absence, 007.
你会到哪去?
Do have any thoughts about where you might go?
我一向都很向往到里约热内卢
I've always had a hankering to go to Rio, sir.
我记得你曾经提过
I think I can recall your mentioning it.
不要再出错否则你我都有麻烦
007, no slipups or we're both in trouble.
我们已经躲过一次小型危机
Yes, a minor crisis has been averted.
问题不大 但从今天开始
No, no, nothing serious, but all merchandise
得改变货物的运送路线
is to be rerouted as from today.
关于查治的代替者方面
Now, regarding a replacement for Cha,
你有适当的人选吗?
do you have someone in mind?
好 若你找到他就最好
Oh, yes, well, if you can get him, of course.
BA128号班机 开往里约热内卢 乘客请从七号闸登机
Flight BA128 to Rio de Janeiro now boarding, gate number seven.
欢迎你来到
Welcome to Rio, Mr. Bond.
- 这是总统套房 - 真的吗?
- The President Suite. - Really?
你不用带我参观了 若我迷路 自会叫计程车
Well, don't bother showing me the rest. If I get lost, I'll take a cab.
- 你也是套房的服务之一?  - 这得看住的是谁了
- Do you come with the suite? - It depends who's renting it.
伏特加马丁尼? 摇动 不要搅拌
Vodka martini? Shaken not stirred.
你干嘛从机场跟踪我来到这里?
Why were you following me from the airport?
我要认识你 我叫曼露娜
I was trying to meet you. My name is Manuela.
我在VH部门工作 有人请我们协助你
I work for Station VH. We have been asked to assist you.
M真是设想周到
M thinks of everything.
请问卡威有什么意思?
Tell me, Manuela, do the initials C and W mean anything to you?
卡威? 是卡洛斯与威斯堡
C and W? Yes, Carlos and Wilmsberg.
是本地很大的进口商
They are very big importers in Rio.
我相信是崔斯工业的子公司
A subsidiary of the Drax Group, I believe.
他们在凯利欧加大道有个仓库
They have a warehouse on Carioca Avenue.
今天晚上我要谨慎地夜访仓库
I'd like to pay it a discreet visit tonight.
今天晚上? 可能会有点困难
Tonight? I think you may find that a little difficult.
困难与否 我们也得去
Difficult or not, it's something we have to do.
与此同时
And meanwhile,
若不跳舞 你会如何打发五小时?
how do you kill five hours in Rio if you don't samba?
- 仓库在那里 - 一个人都没有
- There's the warehouse. - And not a soul about.
- 后面应该有入口 - 好提议
- I think there's a way around the back. - Good thinking.
是这里了
This is it.
别跟陌生人说话 我很快回来
Don't talk to any strange men. I'll be back.
- 你还好吧?  - 我没事 但我情愿与你跳舞
- Are you all right? - Yes, but I'd rather dance with you.
我早说过别跟陌生人说话的
I did tell you not to talk to any strange men.
- 你在里面有发现吗?  - 只有这个
- Did you find anything in there? - Only this.
"崔斯空运"
"Drax Air Freight."
他们在哪个机场运作?
Do you know which airport they operate from?
圣彼得机场 要我带你去吗?
Yes. San Pietro. Do you want me to take you there?
不用了 你需要休息
No, I think you need some rest.
- 我送你回去 - 好的
- Come on. I'll drop you off. - Okay.
- 我们不是见过面的?  - 这副脸孔和态度都很熟悉
- Haven't we met before somewhere? - The face is familiar, as is the manner.
现在比在威尼斯后更冷了
It's become distinctly chilly since Venice.
那是在你离去之前
Well, that was before you walked out on me.
差点被你放在通道上的行李绊倒
Yes, nearly tripping over your suitcase on the way through the door.
那又如何?
So?
为何要浪费时间跟对方作对?
So why waste time working against each other?
我已经看过崔斯在这里的仓库 里面空空如也
I've checked Drax's warehouse in town. It's empty.
意料中事
That's no surprise. Since I've been here,
飞机每两小时开出一班
those planes have been taking off every two hours.
- 他在搬离 - 到哪去?
- Yes. He's moving out. - Where to?
这正是我们要调查的
That's what we're going to find out,
我们得合作找出答案
now that we're working together.
- 我仍然不知道你是否可靠 - 我也不知道你是否可靠
- I still don't know if I trust you. - I don't know if I trust you either.
这样不是更刺激吗?
That's what makes it more exciting, doesn't it?
- 怎么了?  - 我不知道
- What's wrong? - I don't know.
但我们还是离开这里吧
But I'm sure we're better off out than in.
把铁链带走
Bring that chain.
- 撑着点! 詹姆斯 - 我也是这样想
- Hang on, James. - The thought had occurred to me.
我应该料到
I might have guessed.
- 你认识他吗?  - 算不上
- Do you know him? - Not socially.
他叫大钢牙 是杀手
His name's Jaws. He kills people.
铁链给我
Here, give me the chain.
快 抱紧我
Come on. Hang on to me.
跳吧!
Jump.
- 你有受伤吗?  - 只是伤了裁缝的心
- Have you broken something? - Only my tailor's heart.
- 为什么要这样做?  - 你救了我一命
- What was that for? - For saving my life.
你提醒我应多点救你
Remind me to do it more often.
谢了 我们没事
Oh, thank you, but we're in great shape.
对不起
Sorry about that.
詹姆斯!  你像从山上掉下来似的
James! You look as though you've just fallen off a mountain.
你真幽默 钱班霓
Well, it's funny you should say that, Moneypenny.
事实上 我在苐车上
As a matter of fact, I was in a cable car and...
- 算了吧 - 在另一边
- Never mind. - The other courtyard.
- 你来了 007 - 是球吗 Q?
- Ah, there you are, 007. - Balls, Q?
是流星锤 007
Bolas, 007.
- 好极了 建军节那天要准备好 - 是的
- Good. Have that ready for Army Day. - Yes, sir.
- M在哪?  - 在办公室里
- Where's M? - He's in the office over there.
这边走
This way.
- 早安 007 - 早安
- Good morning, 007. - Good morning, sir.
- 你来得正好 请坐 - 谢谢
- You're just in time. Sit down. - Thank you, sir.
- Q有发现 - 好极了
- Q's come up with something. - Splendid.
- 有妙算博士的消息吗?  - 恐怕没有
- Any news of Dr. Goodhead? - Afraid not. Right, Q.
我把你在威尼斯得到的液体 进行分解
Well, it's a breakdown on that phial of liquid you picked up in Venice.
- 你似乎是对的 - 谢谢
- You know, you seem to be right, 007. - Thank you.
那是毒性猛烈的神经毒气 但对动物没影响
It's a highly toxic nerve gas that appears to have no effect on animals.
我可以看看程式吗?
May I see the formula?
这是一种植物的化学程式式
It's a chemical formula of a plant.
黑兰花 一种极为稀有的兰花
Orchideae anegra. A very rare orchid indeed.
人们以为它已绝种
Yes. It was thought to be extinct.
直至一名传教士 在阿犸索可山上把一朵带回来
Until a missionary brought one back from the upper reaches of the Amazoco.
其实是从 塔比拉比河附近带回来
Well, actually he brought it back from the area of the River Tapirape.
做得好 你尽快赶去
Well done, James. You better get up there and fast.
我有东西可以送他过去 若他会照顾它的话
And I've got something to get him there, if 007 can be trusted to look after it.
邦德先生 我要让你痛快的死去 你却藐视我的大计
Mr. Bond, you defy all my attempts to plan an amusing death for you.
你没有运动家的品格
You're not a sportsman, Mr. Bond.
为何你要打断 跟蟒蛇之间的相遇?
Why did you break off the encounter with my pet python?
我发觉他爱上了我
I discovered he had a crush on me.
大钢牙
Jaws.
垦月者一号准备好发射 两分钟后升空
Moonraker One on preset launch program, minus two minutes.
撤回工作人员通道
Retract crew access arm.
通道已经撤回
CAA retracted.
- 传送宇宙飞船的能量 - 内部能量已经传送
- Transfer orbiter power. - Internal power transferred.
启动水压器
Activate hydraulics.
- 水压器已经启动 - 启动辅助能源组件
- Hydraulics activated. - Activate auxiliary power unit.
- 已经启动 - 添加燃料
- APU activated. - LH2 replenish.
- 状态确定 - 替氦气缸加压
- Status confirmed. - Pressurize MPS helium tanks.
气压确定
Helium flight pressure confirmed.
你究竟在干什么?
What exactly are you up to here, Drax?
- 为何是兰花?  - 这是文明的诅咒
- And why the orchids? - The curse of a civilization.
建立这个城市的人并非因战火
It was neither war nor pestilence that wiped out the race
或瘟疫而绝种
who built the great city lying around us.
而是由于他们对这朵花的敬意
It was their reverence for this lovely flower.
他们长期吸入花粉 导致不孕
Because long-term exposure to its pollen caused sterility.
说得对 邦德先生
Correct, Mr. Bond.
你也发觉到 我已把种子改良
As you discovered, I have improved upon sterility.
现在那些种子都坏死了
Those same seeds now yield death.
当然 它对动植物无害 人类得保持大自然的平衡
Not, of course, to animals or plant life. One must preserve the balance of nature.
垦月者号的发射程序开始
Moonraker launch program now commencing.
倒数二十秒
Minus 20 seconds.
- 平衡环 - 已经启动
- SRB gimbal profile. - Activated.
- 冷却帮浦 - 启动
- Cooling pumps. - On.
- 惯性IMU - 确定
- IMU to inertial. - IMU confirmed.
垦月者一号发射升空
Moonraker One, liftoff.
我们已经升空
We have liftoff.
垦月者二号 倒数十秒 九 八 七 六
Moonraker Two, T minus ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
五 四 三 二 一
five, four, three, two, one.
主引擎开动
Main engine start.
垦月者二号发射升空
Moonraker Two, liftoff.
- 垦月者三号 - 垦月者三号发射升空
- Moonraker Three. - Moonraker Three, liftoff.
- 垦月者二号 确认程序 - 程序已确认
- Moonraker Two, confirm program pitch. - PP confirmed.
垦月者四号 开始发射程序
Moonraker Four on preset launch program.
垦月者四号发射升空
Moonraker Four, liftoff.
垦月者一号 投弃燃料缸
Moonraker One, SRB jettison.
已经确定分离
We have separation. Confirmed.
垦月者三号 确认程序
Moonraker Three, confirm program pitch.
垦月者五号 开始发射程序
Moonraker Five, on preset launch program.
- 倒数十秒 - 崔斯 还有一件事
- Minus ten... - Drax, one more thing.
你把太空梭交给美国政府
You delivered a shuttle to the U.S. government,
然后又把它劫持 为什么?
then you hijacked it. Why?
因为我需要它
Because I needed it.
一艘垦月者号 在装配时出现问题
One of my own Moonrakers developed a fault during assembly.
我已经因你而很分心了
Now, you have distracted me enough.
邦德先生在游泳后一定很冷
Jaws, Mr. Bond must be cold after his swim.
带他到保证温暖的地方
Place him where he can be assured of warmth.
- 确定 - 垦月者二号 进入轨道
- Confirmed. - Moonraker Two, go for orbit.
速度每秒钟一千尺
Velocity, 1,000 feet per second.
- 所有系统正常... - 投弃燃料缸
- All systems... - SRB jettison.
分离发动机点火
Separation motors fired.
垦月者五号准备升空
Moonraker Five, cleared for launch.
詹姆斯
James.
谢天谢地 你没事
Thank God, you're safe.
垦月者五号 传送飞船能量
Moonraker Five, transfer orbiter power.
启动水力
Hydraulics activated.
- 启动辅助能源组件 - 已经启动
- Activate auxiliary power unit. - APU activated.
- 添加燃料 - 确定
- LH2 replenish. - Confirm.
即使对死亡 我仍很宽宏大量
Even in death, my munificence is boundless.
当火箭升空时
When this rocket lifts off,
我会把你留在 你私人的火葬场里
I shall be leaving you in your own private crematorium.
邦德先生 妙算博士 再见了
Mr. Bond, Dr. Goodhead, I bid you farewell.
- EPS能源启动 - 能源已经启动
- EPS, power on. - EPS, power confirmed.
到通风口去
Come on, the air vent.
输入气流
Fuel tanks go, and go.
垦月者五号准备就绪
Moonraker Five, preset.
外置LH2压力
External LH2 pressure.
- 撤回工作人员通道 - 已经撤回
- Retract crew access arm. - CAA retracted.
退后 快!
Get back quick.
倒数十秒 九
T minus ten seconds, nine,
七
seven,
- 六 五 四... - 时间刚好
- six, five, four... - Bang on time.
- 四 三 二... - 快点!
- four, three, two... - Come on, quick.
往前爬
Straight on.
垦月者六号的太空技师 准备登船
Moonraker Six, astro-technicians prepare to embark.
重复: 垦月者六号的太空技师 准备登船
I repeat, Moonraker Six astro-technicians, prepare to embark.
- 垦月者五号的人员 - 所有系统正常
- Moonraker Five crew. - All systems go.
垦月者六号 开始发射程序
Moonraker Six, start launch sequence.
- 进入轨迹 - 证实
- Go for orbit. - Confirm.
已经分离
We have separation.
垦月者五号的地面员工 留守岗位
Moonraker Five ground crew stand down.
推力: 680万磅
Thrust 6.8 million pounds.
我们走错方向了
We're going the wrong way.
垦月者六号 发射程序完成
Moonraker Six, preset launch program completed.
驾驶员请到发射地点
Pilots proceed from base to launch area.
太空梭准备好 推进器准备好
Shuttle go. Boosters go.
发射台准备好
Launch pad go.
- 外置L2压力 - 确认每平方英寸21
- External LO2 pressure? - Confirmed, 21 psia.
- 外置LH2压力 - 确认: 42.5
- External LH2 pressure? - Confirmed, 42.5 psia.
- 转入内置能源 - 通道已经撤回
- IECF to internal power. - CAA retracted.
垦月者六号可以升空 倒数十秒
Moonraker Six cleared for launch. T minus 10 seconds.
九 八 七 六 五 四
Nine, eight, seven, six, five, four,
三 二 一 发射!
three, two, one, go.
没事的 飞行程序已预先设定
It's all right. We're on a prearranged flight program.
崔斯在垦月者五号
That's Drax in Moonraker Five.
- 其它人呢?  - 不知道 我们看看
- What about the others? - I don't know. Let's see.
所有太空梭都在平衡的轨道上
We're all on parallel courses.
我们正前去集合地点
So, we must be headed for a rendezvous in orbit.
看看我们的货物是什么
Let's see what cargo we have.
- "动物一双一对的走进去" - 什么意思?
- The animals went in two by two. - What do you mean by that?
这次行动是诺亚方舟
Noah's Ark. This operation.
我们会合了
We're converging.
- 要控制火箭?  - 对 我们正在减速
- Control rockets? - Yes, we're slowing down.
那是什么?
What's that?
雷达上并没有影像
There's no image on the radar scanner.
是太空里的城市 雷达却什么也探测不到
An entire city in space and still nothing on the radar scanner.
- 地球上没有人知道它的存在 - 对
- So nobody on Earth knows it's there. - Right.
崔斯一定有雷达干扰装置
Drax must have a radar-jamming system.
垦月者号 启动靠岸程序
All Moonrakers prepare to initiate docking procedures
保持无线电寂静
and continue radio silence.
垦月者六号 开始人工操作 启动靠岸程序
Moonraker Six, you are now in manual. Initiate docking sequence.
所有太空梭已靠岸 执行启动太空站程序
All shuttles now docked. Execute station activation procedure.
重力维持正常 维生系统正常
Gravity, normal conditions. Life-support system, nominal.
垦月者六号的技师 启动操作程序
Moonraker Six technicians, commence operational sequence.
- 开始程序四 - 检查气闸封口
- Sequence four initiated. - Check airlock seals.
已经关紧
ALS secure.
所有人员请到指挥卫星
All personnel to Command satellite.
所有人员请到M5区
All crews to M5 segment.
垦月者六号的技师 请到M2区
Moonraker Six technicians to M2 segment.
垦月者一号及三号的技师 请到M1区
Moonraker One and Three to M1 segment.
垦月者四号及五号的技师 请到M4区
Moonraker Four and Five to M4 segment.
垦月者二号的技师 请到M5区
Moonraker Two to M5 segment.
第四及第七队 照计划操作
Units four and seven, man console as planned.
第一 三 五及六组 到预先分配好的岗位就位
Units one, three, five and six, assume pre-assigned stations.
- 联线压力 - 确定
- Pressure on-line? - Confirmed.
- 维生系统 - 正常
- Life support? - Normal.
我在威尼斯见过那些圆球 里面充满神经毒气
Those are the globes I saw in Venice with the nerve gas phials inside.
首先是一个梦想 现在它已经成为事实
First there was a dream. Now there is reality.
在这个无污染的天国摇篮里
Here in the untainted cradle of the heavens
一个新的超级民族
will be created a new super-race,
一个拥有完美肉体的种族
a race of perfect physical specimens.
你们被挑选成为他们的祖先 跟众神一样
You have been selected as its progenitors, like gods.
你们的子孙会重返地球 根据自己的形象把它改造
Your offspring will return to Earth and shape it in their image.
你们都是我的王国里的子民
You have all served in humble capacities in my terrestrial empire.
跟你们一样 你们的后代要尊重
Your seed, like yourselves,
这个由我一手创办的王国里
will pay deference to the ultimate dynasty which I alone have created.
从他们在地球上的第一天 他们举头望天
From their first day on Earth they will be able to look up
就会知道在天堂上有法纪和秩序
and know that there is law and order in the heavens.
各单位 开始兰花行动
All units, start Operation Orchid.
若地球的人看的到我们 他们定会调查
If we were visible from Earth, they'd investigate.
你认为雷达干扰系统会在哪?
Where do you suppose that radar-jamming system is?
我们来的时候没经过任何东西 就这边吧
We didn't pass anything on the way here, so let's try this way.
二号岗位 检查座标 第四模式
Station two, check coordinates, mode four.
启动圆球发射计时程序
Initiate globe launch timing sequence.
轨迹发报机 第十层 没有重力
Orbital communicator, level 10. Zero gravity.
是这里了 雷达干扰系统
This is it, the radar-jamming system.
- 协调变换程式 - 有
- Coordinate conversion program. - Check.
- 附属波瓣 - 有
- Side lobe gain. - Check.
- 光谱频率响应 - 有
- Spectral response. - Check.
- 旋转稳定器 修正系数 - 好
- Spin stabilizer correction factor. - Okay.
千兆赫反射器效率
Gigahertz reflector efficiency.
太阳光子过滤器
Solar photon screen.
你在太空总署学会打架的吗?
Where did you learn to fight like that? NASA?
不是 在瓦萨尔
No, Vassar.
- 关上了没有?  - 永久关上了
- Switched off? - Permanently.
地球上的人可以看见我们
Now we can be spotted from Earth.
- 糟透了 - 直径超过二百米
- This doesn't look good at all. - It's over 200 meters in diameter.
是的
Yes, yes.
你听清楚 不是我们放上去的
Will you please listen, General Gogol? We didn't put it up there.
也不是我们干的 史考特上校 你有什么建议?
Neither did we, Colonel Scott. So what are you suggesting?
我们已派了太空船去拦截他们
We've taken action already. We're sending up a vehicle to intercept.
很好 但若十二小时内没有回音
Very well, but if we don't hear from you in the next 12 hours
我们将采取行动 后果由你们负责
we take action ourselves and hold you responsible for the consequences.
保持联络
We'll be in touch, General.
- 抱歉把你弄醒 - 我已经醒了
- Sorry to have woken you. - I was already awake.
我怎么能入睡?  除了烦恼什么都没有
How can I sleep? Nothing but problems.
烦恼 烦恼
Problems, problems.
三名太空人正朝发射台去
Marine astronauts to launch pad.
- B发射程序完成 - 发射一号圆球
- Launch pre-program complete, sir. - Launch globe number one.
地球有太空船升空 在美洲范登堡
T.D.R.S.S. reports a launch, sir. Continental U.S.A. Vandenberg.
应该没有发射计划的 检查雷达干扰系统
There are no launches scheduled. Check radar-jamming system.
怎么了?
Well?
系统电力供应 和后备电源中断了
Jamming power supply and backup have failed, sir.
- 马上调查 - 马上调查28号
- Investigate immediately. - Investigate number 28, immediately.
詹姆斯邦德
James Bond.
你跟一个不可避免的 而且令人厌恶的季节 一同出现
You appear with the tedious inevitability of an unloved season.
我不以为太空里会有季节
I didn't think there were any seasons in space.
对你来说 只会有冬天
As far as you're concerned, only winter.
还有狡猾的妙算博士
And the treacherous Dr. Goodhead.
不管你如何努力阻扰 我的梦想快要成真了
Despite your efforts, my finely wrought dream approaches its fulfillment.
不管你有什么妄想 都不会成真的
Your dream, whatever sort of nightmare it is, hasn't a chance, Drax.
是吗? 我们走着瞧
You think not? We shall see.
第二次发射开始
We're coming up to second launch position.
发射二号圆球
Launch globe number two.
你已经明白我的构想了吧
No doubt you have realized the splendor of my conception.
首先用一条死亡项链围绕地球
First, a necklace of death about the Earth.
五十个圆球 各自在指定地方 释放神经毒气
50 globes, each releasing its nerve gas over a designated area,
每个球体可以杀死一亿人
each capable of killing 100 million people.
这么一来 人类就会绝种
And the human race as you know it will cease to exist.
然后是再生 一个新世界就诞生
Then a rebirth, a new world.
美国的太空船要拦截我们
U.S. spacecraft on course to intercept us, sir.
启动雷射炮 准备把太空船击落
Activate laser. Prepare to destroy spacecraft.
我们绝对有能力保护自己 对付任何敌人
You see, my dear Bond, we're well able to protect ourselves against all enemies.
容我给你介绍 这个没有空气的密室
Allow me to introduce you to the airlock chamber.
看看你从这个世界 走到另一个世界的路线
Observe, Mr. Bond, your route from this world to the next.
还有你 妙算博士
And you, Dr. Goodhead.
你要成为美国首位女太空人 的渴望
Your desire to be America's first woman in space
很快就会实现
will shortly be fulfilled.
把你留在飞行配种站里 接受新种的配种
Leaving you on your flying stud farm, conceiving your new master race?
如果你愿意 是的
If you like, yes.
任何外形达不到 你的完美标准的人
And of course, anyone not measuring up to your standards of physical perfection
- 都会被消灭 - 当然是了
- will be exterminated. - Certainly.
真有趣
Interesting.
有趣极了
Most interesting.
大钢牙 驱逐他们
Jaws, expel them.
你要服从我!
Jaws! You obey me!
驱逐他们!
Expel them!
抓着他们!
Hold them!
美国太空船三分钟后到达
Sir, U.S. spacecraft, three minutes to intercept.
准备消灭他们
Stand by to laser it.
- 启动开火程序 - 已经开动
- Initiate firing sequence. - Initiating.
美国太空船已进入射程范围 二十五点五 正在接近
U.S. spacecraft in laser range, 25.5 and closing.
射程十五
Range 15.
射程十
Range 10.
准备开火 五 四 三 二
Prepare to fire. Five, four, three, two...
它停止转动了
It's stopped rotating.
打开仓库舱门
Open the cargo doors.
第一队 出发
Number one platoon, EVA.
尝试靠岸
Let's try docking.
占领一楼平台!
Colonel Scott will take the first landing!
入侵者在七号卫星着陆
Intruders have docked at satellite seven, sir.
加强守卫 保护来这里的通道
Double the guard at every entrance in this satellite.
报告入侵者 在太空站内的一举一动
Report intruders' progress throughout the space station.
三号圆球已准备好发射
Number three globe ready for launching, sir.
继续下去!
Proceed!
全体人员听着 格杀勿论
Group One, attack enemy. All units shoot to kill.
- 上校 别开火 - 别开枪!
- Colonel Scott, don't shoot. - Hold your fire.
渗入五号走廊 入侵者正向指挥卫星进发
Corridor five penetrated. Intruders advancing on Command satellite.
第三区需要维修人员
Maintenance crew needed, section three.
最少我很乐意 除掉你这伙眼中钉
At least I shall have the pleasure of putting you out of my misery.
很凄凉吧? 邦德先生
Desolated, Mr. Bond?
使人心碎 崔斯先生
Heartbroken, Mr. Drax.
容许我
Allow me.
为人类跨出一大步
Take a giant step for mankind.
- 崔斯在哪?  - 他必须要去飞行了
- Where's Drax? - He had to fly.
史考特怎么了?
How's Scott doing?
他已控制了指挥卫星
He's got control of the Command satellite.
发射圆球的装置已经关闭
We put the launching gear for the globes out of action.
当太空站解体时 它们也会分解
When the station breaks up, they'll disintegrate. They'll harm no one.
剩下的三个 也足以干掉数百万人
But the three that have gone, they'll kill millions.
一定要把它们消灭
Those three must be destroyed.
来吧!
Come on!
快叫你的部下离开这里!
Colonel, get your men off as quickly as possible.
任务已经完结
Your mission is completed.
马上命令手下返回太空梭!
Sergeant, round up your men, get them back to the shuttle. Fast!
返回太空梭 马上离开!
Back to the shuttle, everybody! On the double!
垦月者5号配备有雷射枪
Moonraker Five, that's the answer. Drax's shuttle is armed with a laser.
我们可以追踪并摧毁圆球
We can track those globes and destroy them.
没希望了 走廊被封住了 他们无法来到
It's hopeless, sir. The corridor's blocked. They can't get to us now.
我们走吧
All right, let's go.
发射系统被卡住了
Docking release system is jammed.
松开门锁 我尝试用人工操作
Release the door lock. I'll see if I can operate it manually.
也失灵了
It's jammed too.
为我们干杯
Well, here's to us.
大钢牙? 我们无法离开 发射系统被卡住了
Jaws, we can't disengage. The docking release system is jammed.
你能帮忙吗?
Can you help us?
我们脱身了
We're free.
他们没事的 这里距离地球 只有一百里
Don't worry, they'll make it. It's only 100 miles to Earth.
寻找圆球的下落
Let's get a read-out on those globes.
银幕上有影像了 我们很快就会看到圆球
I have the three globes on the screen. We should have a visual in a minute.
在这里
There it is.
雷射枪自动瞄准目标 密码945 准备好
The laser's on automatic. Code 945 set.
击落一个 还有两个
One down, two to go.
二号就在前面
Number two straight ahead.
怎么了?
What is it?
我们在大气层表面掠过
We're skipping on the Earth's atmosphere.
进入射程
In range.
- 很快就会看见最后一个 - 在那里
- We should see the last one soon. - There it is.
- 越来越热了 - 我也束手无策
- It's getting hot. - It can't be helped.
我们比原定轨道来得倾斜
I'm coming in at a steeper angle than I should in order to catch that last globe.
我无法继续保持这条航道 我们会在二千万尺上空解体
I can't hold this course much longer. We'll break up at 200,000 feet.
给我多一点时间
Just a few seconds more.
自动点火系统失灵 一定是高热 改由人工操作
Automatic firing system negative. Must be the heat. Switching to manual.
操纵装置没有反应
Controls aren't responding.
- 机翼开始燃烧 - 别摇动
- The wings are beginning to glow. - Just hold her steady.
稳住
Steady.
它要进入地球大气层了 这是最后一次机会了 詹姆斯
It's entering Earth's atmosphere! James, this is our last chance.
稳住
Steady.
史考特上校在太空站中 救回两名生还者
Colonel Scott reports picking up two survivors from the space station,
是一个高个子和矮小的金发妞
a tall man and a short blonde woman.
好的
Right. Okay.
妙算博士在二十分钟前 报告过位置
Dr. Goodhead reported their position 20 minutes ago.
他们已进入我们在太平洋的 追踪船的范围
They're just coming into range of our tracking ship in the Pacific Ocean.
我们很快可以接收到
We should have audiovisual within a few minutes
他们的影像
from the remote onboard TV monitors.
休斯顿呼叫妙算博士 休斯顿呼叫 请确定位置
Houston calling Dr. Goodhead. Houston calling. Confirm your position.
这是英美两国首次联合行动
As this is the first joint venture between our two countries,
我把影像直接传送到 白宫和白金汉宫
I'm having it patched directly to the White House and Buckingham Palace.
我确定女皇陛下会很着迷
Well, I'm sure Her Majesty will be fascinated.
- 还有视听划面 - 终于有了
- We have audiovisual. - Ah, at last.
- 007 - 天啊 邦德在干嘛?
- 007. - My God, what's Bond doing?
他在尝试重新进入
I think he's attempting re-entry, sir.
- 詹姆斯?  - 是时候回家了
- James? - I think it may be time to go home.
再带我环游世界一次
Take me round the world one more time.
有何不可?
Why not?